<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stat-cz.github.io</id>
    <title>Gridea</title>
    <updated>2020-04-29T17:07:10.589Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stat-cz.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://stat-cz.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>温故而知新</subtitle>
    <logo>https://stat-cz.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://stat-cz.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, Gridea</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CV]]></title>
        <id>https://stat-cz.github.io/post/cv/</id>
        <link href="https://stat-cz.github.io/post/cv/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-04-29T11:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="zhang-haoshi">ZHANG HAOSHI</h1>
<p>May 25, 1991<br>
+086-15901109556<br>
zhs2016@buaa.edu.cn<br>
No. 37 Xueyuan Road, Haidian District, Beijing, P.R. China, 100083</p>
<h3 id="education-background">EDUCATION Background</h3>
<h4 id="spe2016-present-beihang-university-phd-student">Spe.2016-Present Beihang University PhD student</h4>
<p>Solid state physics, matrix analysis.</p>
<h4 id="sep-2015-jul-2016-beihang-university-master-student">Sep. 2015-Jul. 2016 Beihang University Master student</h4>
<p>Advanced optics, fiber optics, photo electromagnetism, laser principle, fiber-optic gyroscope, advanced digital signal processing, numerical analysis method, academic English writing.</p>
<h4 id="spe2010-jul-2014-chongqing-university-undergraduate-student">Spe.2010- Jul. 2014 Chongqing University Undergraduate student</h4>
<p>College physics, advanced mathematics, engineering optics, photoelectronic, automatic control theory, signal and system, analog circuit, digital circuit, computer science and programing, mechanics.</p>
<h3 id="research-interest">RESEARCH INTEREST</h3>
<p>Irradiation characteristic of optical fiber and its temperature dependence.</p>
<p>Irradiation resistance of optical fiber, devices, and sensors.</p>
<p>Distributed temperature and irradiation sensing;</p>
<p>Shape sensing with multi-core fiber Bragg gratings.</p>
<h3 id="publications">PUBLICATIONS</h3>
<p>[1] Jin Jing, Zhang Haoshi, etc, Distributed Temperature Sensing Based on Rayleigh Scattering in Irradiated Optical Fiber, IEEE Sensors Journal, 2016.10.7, 16(24): 8928~8935.</p>
<p>[2] Jin Jing, Zhang Ting, Ma Kun, Zhang Haoshi, etc, Fault Diagnosis of Space-Borne Fiber-Optic Gyros Based on Random Walk Coefficient Prediction and In-Orbit Calculation, IEEE Sensors Journal, 2017.10.15, 17(20): 6637~6645.</p>
<p>[3] Zhang haoshi, etc. Temperature dependence of RIA in optical fiber: a solution for temperature sensing. OFS, 2018.9.</p>
<p>[4] Cryogenic temperature sensing based on temperature dependence of color centers in optical fiber. (under review)</p>
<p>[5] Loss Prediction of Three-level Amplified Spontaneous Emission (ASE) Sources in Radiation Environment (under writing)</p>
<h3 id="honors-and-awaerds">HONORS and AWAERDS</h3>
<p>International collegiate spacecraft innovation design contest 2018, second prize.</p>
<p>Award-winning works：3D Shape Sensing Technology for Deformable Structures of Spacecraft Based on Multi-core Fiber.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>